

# Corentin Job - Game Designer

**LEVELDESIGN COMBATDESIGN NARRATIVEDESIGN SYSTEMDESIGN** 

+33781379711 - job.corentin.pro@gmail.com - Portfolio: https://jobcorentin89.github.io/

Professional Game Designer with 3 years of experience, I design creative game experiences in collaboration with teams of professional. Specialized in system design, level design, and gameplay iteration, I've worked on several projects from prototyping to final implementation. I focus on optimizing mechanics and creating immersive experiences. I enjoy teamwork, testing and iterating on ideas, refining concepts through playtests, always with one goal in mind: to create gameplay that's not only well-designed but genuinely fun to play.

#### Professional Experiences

- @ Roqueside **Unannounced Project** - Game designer
- Aug. 2023 to Dec. 2024
- @ Hibernian Workshop **Astral Ascent**
- Game designer and QA Aug. 2021 to June 2023

- Designed and documented game systems and mechanics.
- Prototyped concepts during short production cycles in Unity.
- Organized and scheduled production timelines.
- Responsible for the overall game design vision.
- Conducted **playtest sessions** with the community to **gather feedback**.
- Designed and balanced game mechanics and systems aligned with the Game Director's
  - Conducted **playtest sessions** with the community to **gather feedback**.
  - Iterated through gameplay improvements based on QA tests.

## Students Projects

- @ Rubika **Fall Garden**
- Lead Game designer

Feb. 2021 to May 2021

- @ Rubika **Pirate Academy**
- Lead Game designer

Nov. 2020 to Jan. 2021

@ Summer Stage Akuma: wrath of the fallen - Lead Game Designer

June 2020 to Aug. 2020

- Design of the character controller, enemies (AI and patterns) and level design.
- Implementation of visual effects and post process in Unity.
- Organised production plannings and task for each members.
- Collaboration with a teams of 8 designers and artists.
- Design **system and mechanics** for the game.
- In charge of the **project vision** with **2 other designers**.
- Collaboration with 45 members (designer, artist and programmers.)
- Design and complete **implementation of a mini-game in Unity** (SFX iand music included)
- Project mainly made **remote at home**. (Covid)
- Design and documentation of the game main systems.
- In charge of the **project vision**.
- Collaboration with a team of 8 designers and artits.

#### Education =

**Bachelor Game Design** @Rubika - Valenciennes Sept. 2018 to May 2021

**MANAA** @LISAA - Rennes

Sep. 2017 to May 2018 Science Baccalauréat

@Lycée Ernest Renan Sep. 2016 to June 2017

- Learned all of game design fundamentals
- Worked on multiple game projects (board games and video games)
- Specialized in system and combat design
- Studied drawing with various mediums and techniques
- Final year project focused on video games
- Studied art history from Antiquity to the 20th century
- Specialization: Earth and Life Sciences
- Took evening drawings courses alongside studies

## Skills and Tools

- English (C1)
- Unity (Prototyping, assets and SFX integration)
- Construct 3 (Prototyping, assets and SFX integration)
- Godot
- Blender (3D modeling, Rigging, Animation)
- GitHub/GitKraken (Versioning)

- Adobe Suite(Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign)
- Documentation (Miro, Google doc / sites)
- Playtest Methodology (lead playtest, feedback)
- Scope (planification, ressource management)
- Team work
- Agile Method